Shubhashis Das Salami Bypass, Bhadrak, Odisha, 756100, India +91 9658240924 shubhashisdash95@gmail.com

Dear Sir/Madam,

I am grateful for the opportunity to apply for the Sales & Marketing position of your organization. Marketing has been my lifelong passion, and I graduated with a three year Degree. Marketing is a full-time commitment, and it is essential to always look for ways to improve a company's outreach. A successful marketing campaign is crucial to the long-term success of any company, and I believe that my unique skill set is perfect for this job.

I oversaw a wide variety of successful marketing campaigns. My primary goal was to increase brand awareness and reach new clients through social media, seo practices, and traditional advertising platforms. Each marketing campaign was successful in raising interest and interaction with potential clients. I was able to achieve each marketing goal by working with other employees in a team-focused environment.

Reaching marketing goals is always a top priority, and I am always looking out for the best interests of the company. I enjoy delivering marketing presentations to potential clients and focusing on the strengths of an organization. I am never satisfied with the status quo, and I believe that a company should continually look for ways to improve and reach new clients through innovative campaigns.

Thank you for taking the time to read my cover letter. I hope to speak with you soon and learn more about the opportunities for a Marketing position at Retail Ocean. Working in the marketing field is a fantastic opportunity, and I believe that I am a great fit at Retail Ocean with my unique skill set and prior experience.

Sincerely,

Shubhashis Das

- +91 9658240924
- shubhashisdash95@gmail.
- Salami Bypass, Bhadrak Odisha, 756100,India



# Shubhashis Das

## **About Me**

On my educational & practical experience, Typical responsibilities listed on a Sales And Marketing Executive conducting market research, monitoring competition, writing reports, organizing promotional activities, and managing campaigns on social media. Marketing opportunities are based on dicipline, coordination which I believe in my practical knowledge.



## Education

2001 - 2013 M.M.Saraswati Shishu Vidya Mandir, Nayabazar,

Bhadrak | H.S.E

Stanford people take on audacious problems, bring imaginative new approaches to solving them, and work collaboratively to advance knowledge and make meaningful contributions to our

2013 - 2015 Bhadrak Autonomou (Junior) College, Bhadrak |

I.Com

I gain some practical & education knowledge which is helpful of your System.

2015 - 2018 Vyasanagar Autonomous College, Jaipur Road,

Jajpur | B.Com

From here the knowledge which was developed over the period was got polished as well.



Experience

2018 - 2021

### LIC premium Point | Marketing Executive

In the period after joining this organization I got vast knowledge of Marketing science & managerial ability and interviewing skills.

02-2021 - 08-2021

# Jana Small Finance Bank (Third-Party) | Marketing Officer

Day by day the experience & solidity polished and here it's helpful to me.



# **Projects**

09-2021 - 12-2021

# TPNODL | Meter Replacement (Kandhamal District)

As a role of project manager was a tough responsibility for me but which was aslo taught me many things in every angle, rather my past experiences helped me in this project to complete the process before the deadline(01.2022) which provides me mental pleasure and willingness to get my works done through.



### Other Info

### Skills

Hard Working, Good Communication Skill, Motivative, Adaptability, Quick Learner, Push Sales.

### Languages

Idea, English, Hindi

#### **Awards**

Best App of the year

### Interest

Traveling, Driving, Thinking of New & Innovative Ideas, Music.

Shubhashis Das